How do you think
everything went today? I feel like it
was a great day overall. It was a
blessing to come out here and compete
with my guys one last time. And I feel
like everybody put their best foot
forward today. Nice. What about what
about you specifically? Did you
achieve kind of what you wanted to in
front of these NFL scouts? In some areas
I definitely feel like I achieved what
what I wanted to.
I'll probably say on the jumps I could
have done a little bit better, but other
than that I feel like I showed them that
I can move well at my size and things
like that. You trained in Tennessee for
this service.
>> Yes, sir. How did that go? How much you
feel like that helped you?
>> It helped me a lot. We had a great
coaching staff out there in not
Franklin, Tennessee in the Nashville
area at D1. And it was a great
experience.
How many
NFL teams have you met with so far in
this process and what's that been like?
The the interviews and the the meetings
and that kind of that kind of deal. Here
lately I've just been filling out a lot
of like the kind of like the paperwork
and the questionnaires and things like
that, but I leave all that to my agent.
I'm just worried about just putting my
best foot forward on the field. Do you
have any visits scheduled? I got to do
the Saints local day Friday, so that's
all I have as of now that I know of.
What do you feel like your chances are
for for getting drafted at this point? I
feel like I definitely have a good shot
at getting drafted. I feel like my my
film speaks for itself. With a lot of
production over the years, so they'll
definitely be getting somebody with a
lot of experience.
How do you think you grew the most this
year with with Tulane this season in in
2025? Just my overall preparation, just
more hours in the film room,
stretching on my own, putting in the
extra work, and just getting in extra
lifts and things like that. Make sure
just taking care of my body overall.
What would you say your biggest asset
is? If an NFL team is looking at you,
what would you say to them? My biggest
asset is being able to keep the guys off
the QB, being able to mirror guys in
pass protection with my great feet and
elite hands. So, definitely you'll be
getting somebody that can keep your
quarterback off off the ground.
How do you think Tulane's prepared you
for you know the next level? I feel like
Tulane definitely prepared me
for the next level. We had a great
obviously a great staff, a great
coaching staff that pushed you to be
your very best each and every day.
Our strength staff was amazing and our
on the field work was just overall
great.